thinkful.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy · Thinkful

Please read this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) fully and carefully before using www.thinkful.com (the “Site”) and/or any of the other services, features, content or applications offered by Thinkful, Inc. (“we”, “us” or “our”) (together with the Site, the “Services”). BY ACCESSING ANY PART OF THE SERVICE, YOU ARE AGREEING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OUR TERMS OF SERVICE (THE “TERMS OF SERVICE”). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY OF THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE SERVICE. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Services, including, without limitation, users who are simply visiting or browsing the Site and users who are contributors of content, information, and other materials or services, registered or otherwise.

We may, at our sole discretion, modify this Privacy Policy at any time. By accessing the Service at any time after such modifications, you are agreeing to such modifications. This Privacy Policy was last modified as of February 23, 2013.

What Personally Identifiable Information Does Thinkful Collect?

We collect the following types of personally identifiable information:

  1. User Provided Information: You may affirmatively provide us with certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, phone number, postal address, credit card information, etc.) when participating in various activities on the Service.
  2. Information Collected by “Cookies”: When you access the Service, we may send one or more “cookies” to your computer. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your browser, which we use to help provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We may use cookies for many purposes, including (without limitation) to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Service, and to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests.
  3. Log File Information: Our servers automatically record certain information that your browser sends whenever you access the Service. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  4. Information Collected by “Clear GIFs”: We may employ "clear GIFs" (a.k.a. Web Beacons), which are used to track usage patterns anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

How Does Thinkful Use Personally Identifiable Information?

Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (in messages, within your public profile page, through User Content that you submit, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

If you have not opted out from receiving these communications from us, we may use your email address, phone number or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages. We also may use your email address, phone number, postal address and other personally identifiable information for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Service changes or for customer service purposes). You cannot opt out of receiving communications for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We use aggregated information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Service and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. In addition, we may use “cookies,” clear gifs and log file information to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests, and remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Service.

Will Thinkful Share Personally Identifiable Information with Others?

We will not share your personally identifiable information with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We may provide personally identifiable information to employees, consultants, affiliates or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. In such circumstances, we require that these parties agree to protect the confidentiality of such information and to comply in all respects with this Privacy Policy.

We may share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Service.

In addition, we may release personally identifiable information: (i) to the extent we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any applicable law, enforce any provision of the Terms of Service, protect ourselves against any liability, defend ourselves against any claims, protect the rights, property and personal safety of any user or protect the public welfare; or (ii) to respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

Third Party Advertisers

We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Service. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to them, and we cannot control their activities.

Is My Information Secure?

We have implemented security measures to protect personally identifiable information collected on the Service against loss, misuse or alteration. In addition, your account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. It is important that you protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Moreover, despite the precautions described above, we cannot and do not guarantee that the individual user information you have transmitted will not be intercepted by others and/or decrypted or accidentally disclosed, and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 13 years old to register to use the Service.

Special Note to International Users

The Service is hosted in the United States and is primarily intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are accessing the Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Service, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Service, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of the Service who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail with "California Privacy Rights" in the heading to hello@thinkful.com or write us at:

Thinkful Privacy Rights  
304 Hudson, Suite 505  
New York, NY  
10013
